

Contact



artemdanilow95@gmail.com



+48797667497

Skills

- HTML
- Css, Sass
- Tailwindcss
- Javascript
- ReactJS
- Next.js
- Alpine.js
- Strapi CMS
- Statamic CMS
- Figma
- Git

Languages

- polish (C2)
- russian (C2)
- english (B2)

Hobby

- Tricking
- Sport gymnastics
- Travels

Artem Danilov

Frontend developer

About me

I am passionate about programming and creating beautiful things. I have been programming for three years, and for the past two years, I have been working on commercial projects. Over the last six months, I have focused on learning React, Next.js, and Typescript technologies.

Experience

4DMIND

Frontend developer | 02.2021 - 02.2023

- Creating i editing web pages, using technologies such as: HTML, CSS, Javascript, TailwindCss, Alpine.js
- Creating reusable components
- Migration from the old to the new version of CMS
- Migration from other CMS
- Improvement performance and SEO
- Creating documentations
- Introducing customers to the system
- Support for customers from Poland and abroad

GRAWITACJA SPORT ACADEMY (EXTRA JOB)

Acrobatics instructor | 05.2018 - obecnie

- Teaching elements of acrobatics/gymnastics
- Conducting personal and group classes for children

Education

WIT WARSAW SCHOOL OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Bachelor of Engineering | 2023

specialisation: IT Management

POST-SECONDARY COLLEGE OF SPORT MEDICINE

Vocational education | 2017 - 2019

specialisation: Massage therapist

Portfolio

4DMIND.COM

RAPIDROBOTICS.COM

NORTHENDEAVOR.COM

HIGHLANDSOLUTIONS.COM

MATHRIDERS.PL

